{
    "subject": "resource/Team_Bondi",
    "predicate": "ontology/location",
    "object": "resource/Sydney",
    "human_readable": "Team Bondi is located in Sydney.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9468017816543579,
            "question": "Is Team Bondi a local company to Sydney?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9134325981140137,
            "question": "Where is Team Bondi located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.862162172794342,
            "question": "In which country is Team Bondi situated?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8608776330947876,
            "question": "Are there other notable companies located in Sydney besides Team Bondi?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8593072295188904,
            "question": "Does Team Bondi have any branches outside of Sydney?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.59502112865448,
            "question": "What city is the home of Team Bondi?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3686210513114929,
            "question": "What type of organization is Team Bondi?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1210741400718689,
            "question": "What is the population of Sydney?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.10735241323709488,
            "question": "What industries are prominent in Sydney?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.07295075803995132,
            "question": "Is Sydney known for its technology sector?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Team Bondi is located in Sydney.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7320_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What industries are prominent in Sydney?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7320_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the population of Sydney?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7320_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of organization is Team Bondi?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7320_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7320_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7320_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7320_148.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7320_149.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7320_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7320_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7320_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7320_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7320_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7320_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here's the structured JSON response:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nExplanation: The context information mentions that Team Bondi is an Australian game studio based in Sydney, Australia. This supports the triple \"Team Bondi is located in Sydney\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents mention that Team Bondi was an Australian game studio based in Sydney, Australia. This supports the statement that Team Bondi is located in Sydney."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}